Guide to the Amos Poe Papers, 1966-2005 MSS.203
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Writing
  - Series I, Subseries A: Scripts and Screenplays
    - "Kenny Makes A Move" by Brian Kistler and Amos Poe, February 2001 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - "Kenny Makes A Move" by Brian Kistler and Amos Poe [With Annotation and Inserts], March 2001 - January 2004 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - "Kid Killer" by Amos Poe and Nick Tiger, June 15, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - "Kid Killer" by Amos Poe and Nick T. Poe, June 1992 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - "Kid Killer" by Amos Poe and Nick Tiger, June 1992 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - "Kid Killer" by Amos Poe and Nick T. Poe [With Notes], June 1992 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - "Kid Killer" by Amos Poe and Nick T. Poe [Alex R.'s Copy with Notes], June 1992 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - "Kid Killer" by Amos Poe and Nick Tiger, April 25, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - "Kid Killer" by Amos Poe [With Notes], 1998 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - "Kid Superstar and the Beggar Boy" by Amos Poe [1st Draft], August 1992 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - "The Kindness of Stranglers" by Amos Poe, November 2000 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - "Ladies' Man" by Amos Poe and Brian Kistler [1st Draft with Images], March 17,, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - "Ladies' Man, Pilot Episode: Kenny Makes A Move" by Amos Poe and Brian Kistler [With Annotation], March 2004 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - "Ladies' Man, Pilot Episode: Kenny Makes A Move" by Amos Poe and Brian Kistler, May 14, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - "La Pacifica" by Amos Poe and Joel Rose [With Annotation], June 1991 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - "La Pacifica" by Amos Poe and Joel Rose, June 1991 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - "La Pacifica" by Amos Poe and Joel Rose [Draft III], October 1991 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - "La Pacifica" by Amos Poe and Joel Rose, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - "La Pacifica" by Amos Poe and Joel Rose [Draft IV], December 1991 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - "La Pacifica" by Amos Poe and Joel Rose [Graphic Novel Script], 1993 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - "La Pacifica" by Amos Poe and Joel Rose [Graphic Novel Script with Corrections], 1993 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - "La Pacifica" by Amos Poe and Joel Rose, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - "La Pacifica" by Amos Poe and Joel Rose [4th Draft with Annotation], undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - "The Listener" by Amos Poe [1st Draft], February 1994 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - "The Listener" by Amos Poe [1st Draft with Annotation], February 1994 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - "The Listener" by Amos Poe [2nd Draft], March 1994 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - "The Listener" by Amos Poe [2nd Draft with Notes], March 1994 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - "The Listener" by Amos Poe [III], undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - "The Listener" by Amos Poe [III], undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - "The Lodz Seven" by Amos Poe [1st Draft], January 1993 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - "The Lodz Seven" by Amos Poe [With Annotation], undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - "The Lodz 7" by Amos Poe, undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - "Losing My Religion" by Abdul O'Toole, March 2001 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - "Lost in the Forest" by Amos Poe [Partial], November 1995 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - "Marty Timberland" by Amos Poe, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - "The Midnight Show" by Amos Poe [Producer Melissa Lamb, Director John A. Gallagher, Based on Story by Richard Dollison and William Coleman], 1982 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - "Moses" by Amos Poe, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - "Mrs. Dogg" by Amos Poe [With Annotation], January 1990 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - "Mrs. Dogg" by Amos Poe [With Annotation], January 1990 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - "Mrs. Dogg" by Amos Poe [2nd Draft with Annotation], February 1991 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - "Mrs. Dogg" by Amos Poe [2nd Draft with Annotation], February 1991 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - "Mrs. Dogg" by Amos Poe [III], April 1991 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - "Mrs. Dogg" by Amos Poe [III with Annotation], April 1991 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - "Mrs. Dogg" by Amos Poe [I - III with Annotation], 1990 - 1991 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - "Mrs. Dogg" by Amos Poe [V], April 1993 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - "Mrs. Dogg" by Amos Poe [V with Annotation], April 1993 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - "Mrs. Dogg" by Amos Poe [VI with Notes], May 1993 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - "(Mrs. Dogg III) The Mrs." by Amos Poe, September 1995 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - "(Mrs. Dogg III) The Mrs." by Amos Poe [With Annotation], September 1995 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - "Mrs. Dogg" by Amos Poe [VI with Annotation], May 1996 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - "Mrs. Dogg" by Amos Poe [#7], 1996 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - "Mrs. Dogg" by Amos Poe [#8], May 1996 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - "Mrs. Dogg" by Amos Poe [#10], August 1996 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - "Mrs. Dogg" by Amos Poe [#11], September 1996 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - "Mrs. Dogg" by Amos Poe [#12], October 1996 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - "Mrs. Dogg" by Amos Poe [With Annotation], 1996 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - "Mrs. Dogg" by Amos Poe [III], undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - "Mrs. Dogg" by Amos Poe [III], undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - "Mrs. Dogg" by Amos Poe [4th Draft with Annotation], undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - "Night and the City" by Richard Price [Revised Draft], undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - "Night Witches" Original Screenplay by Brian Clemens, Written by April Holloway and Alexander Siddig, June 22, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - "The Night Witches" by Amos Poe [Preliminary Draft For Comment, with Frixos Constantine's Notes], March 8, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - "Night Witches" by Amos Poe, June 2002 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - "Night Witches" by Amos Poe [With Annotation], 2002 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - "Night Witches" by Amos Poe [May 10, 2002 Draft with Annotation] (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - "Night Witches" by Amos Poe [Partial with Annotation], 2002 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - "1 Kiss 2 Many" Screenplay by Amos Poe, Story by Alain Klarer, December 1998 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - "Only In America (Tides)" by Amos Poe [2nd Draft, 1st Draft Title: "Beach House"], January 7, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - "Only in America" by Amos Poe [2nd Draft, 1st Draft Title: "Beach House"], January 13, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - "Paint. It Black." by Amos Poe, Based on the Screenplay by Jay McInerney [2nd Draft], December 31, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - "Paint. It Black." by Amos Poe [With Annotation], undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - "Paint. It Black" by Amos Poe [Handwritten], undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - "The Piano Tuner" by Alex Kalman and Nick Poe, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - "Port of Call" by Amos Poe [Original Draft, Mock-Up], January - February 1988 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - "Port of Call" by Amos Poe [Original Draft, Mock-up], January - February 1988 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - "Port of Call" by Amos Poe [2nd Draft], March 1, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - "Port of Call" by Amos Poe [2nd Draft with Annotation], March 1, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - "Port of Call" by Amos Poe [3rd Draft], September 30, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - "Port of Call" by Amos Poe [3rd Draft with Annotation], September 30, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - "Port of Call" / "Weeping Willow" by Amos Poe [With Annotation], September 30, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - "Port of Call" by Amos Poe, September 30, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - "Port of Call" by Amos Poe, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - "The Prince and the Pauper" by Amos Poe [With Annotation], September 1992 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - "The Prince and the Pauper" by Amos Poe [With Annotation], September 1992 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - "The Prince and the Pauper" by Amos Poe [With Annotation], September 1992 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - "The Prince and the Pauper" by Amos Poe [Revised 1st Draft], October 1992 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - "The Prince and the Pauper" by Amos Poe [2nd Draft], March 1993 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - "The Prince and the Pauper" by Amos Poe [3rd Draft], June 1993 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - "The Prince and the Pauper" by Amos Poe [Partial], undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - "Pronto!" by Amos Poe, January 2005 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - "Q & A" by Sidney Lumet, From the Novel by Edwin Torres [Revised Final Draft], August 25, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - "Raising Arizona" by Joel Coen and Ethan Coen [Revised 1st Draft], 1985 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - "The Revolution Is Under Construction" by J.J. Kennedy and Leonardo Ricagni [With Annotation], undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - "Rocket Gibraltar" by Amos Poe [With Treatment and Annotation], 1985 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - "Rocket Gibraltar" by Amos Poe [Original Revised 1st Draft], May 15, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - "Rocket Gibraltar" by Amos Poe [Revised 1st Draft], May 15, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - "Rocket Gibraltar" by Amos Poe [Revised 1st Draft], May 15, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - "Rocket Gibraltar" by Amos Poe [Mark-Up], 1987 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - "Rocket Gibraltar" by Amos Poe [2nd Draft], May 1, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - "Rocket Gibraltar" by Amos Poe [2nd Draft], May 1, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - "Rocket Gibraltar" by Amos Poe [3rd Draft with Annotation], July 17, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - "Rocket Gibraltar" by Amos Poe [4th Draft With New Scene Numbers], July 21, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - "Rocket Gibraltar" by Amos Poe, undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - "Rocket Gibraltar" by Amos Poe [Original Draft/Partial], undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - "Rocket Gibraltar" by Amos Poe [Fragments], undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - "Rules of the Road" by Amos Poe, March 1995 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - "Sam the Man" / "Nowhere Man" by Paul Kneubuhl [1st Draft with Notes], October 30, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - "Sam the Man" / "Nowhere Man" by Paul Kneubuhl [2nd Draft], December 29, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - "Sam the Man"/ "Nowhere Man" by Paul Kneubuhl [With Annotation], January 31, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - ("Sam the Man") / "Nowhere Man" by Paul Kneubuhl and Amos Poe [1st Draft with Annotation], March 1997 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - "Sam the Man" / "Nowhere Man" by Amos Poe and Paul Kneubuhl, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - "The Savage Garden" by Amos Poe [Original, Mark-Up], 1987 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - "Scout's Honor" by Amos Poe [2nd Draft], February 1993 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - "Scout's Honor" by Amos Poe, undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - "Shame The Stars That Glow (funk)" by Amos Poe, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - "(Scott Cohen in) Silk City" by Amos Poe, November 2005 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - "Silk City" by Amos Poe [With Notes], 2003, November 2005 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - "Silk City" by Amos Poe [With Annotation], December 2005 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - "Silk" by Amos Poe [With Jen's Notes], January 2006 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - "Silk" by Amos Poe [With Marc's Notes], January 2006 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - "Stakeout" by Abdul O'Toole, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - "The Story of Junk" by Linda Yablonsky [Revised], August 30, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - "The Story of Junk" by Linda Yablonsky [With Annotation], August 30, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - "Stunning" by Amos Poe [Handwritten], 1989 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - "Stunning" by Amos Poe, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - "Subway Riders" by Amos Poe [Original Draft, Music Script and Writer's Guild Copyright], 1979 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - "Subway Riders" by Amos Poe [Original], 1979 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - "Sunset Park" by Evan Hunter [Rewrite], October 19, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - "Sunset Park" by John Manniel, Alan Wagner, and Jonathan Latt: Episode "Choosing Sides" [1st Draft], June 30, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - "Toni Morrison's Tar Baby" by Amos Poe [Work Copy], November 1993 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - "Toni Morrison's Tar Baby" by Amos Poe, November 1993 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - "Tar Baby" by Amos Poe [I, With Annotation], November 1993 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - "Tar Baby" by Amos Poe [With Annotation], December 1993 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - "Tar Baby" by Amos Poe and Willy Rameau [With Annotation], November 13, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - "Tar Baby" by Amos Poe, undated (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - "The Theresa Stern Story" by Richard Hell/Meyers, July 7, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - "The Tides" by Amos Poe [3rd Draft with Annotation, 1st Draft Title: "Beach House," 2nd Draft Title: "Only In America"], March 7, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - "The Tides" by Amos Poe [3rd Draft], March 7, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - "The Tides" by Amos Poe [Outs-Script with Inserts], undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - "To Kill An Angel" by Amos Poe, c1986 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - "To Kill An Angel" by Amos Poe, September 1998 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - "To Kill An Angel" by Amos Poe, June 2001 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - "Tomesha" [No Author], undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - "Trash (Pick It Up; Don't Throw Your Life Away)" by Marty Thau, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - "Triple Bogie On A Par Five Hole" by Amos Poe [II with Annotation], November 7, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - "Triple Bogey (on a par five hole)" by Amos Poe, July 4, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - "Triple Bogey On A Par Five Hole" by Amos Poe, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - "Underage" by Amos Poe and Dirk Wittenborn, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - "Underage" by Amos Poe and Dirk Wittenborn, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - "Underage" by Amos Poe and Dirk Wittenborn, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - "Underage" by Amos Poe and Dirk Wittenborn, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - "Underage" by Amos Poe and Dirk Wittenborn, undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - "Unmade Beds" by Amos Poe, undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - "Voodoo Child" by Amos Poe [Work Copy with Annotation}, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - "The Water King" by Amos Poe, June 2003 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - "The Water King" by Amos Poe, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - "The Water Man" by Amos Poe [1st Draft], June 2003 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - "Watch Out!" by Amos Poe, undated (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - "White Gods / The Plumed Serpent - Cortez" [No Author], undated (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - "Xodus 5" by Amos Poe, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - [Unidentified Script], undated (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Series I, Subseries B: Film Treatments, Notes and Notebooks
    - "About a Boy" by Abdul o'Toole [Screen Treatment of "About a Boy" by Patti Smith], February 2001 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - "[The Saga of] Agent Breaker" by Amos Poe, February 7, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - "A.K.A. Rosebud" by Steven Starr and Patrick Dillon [Synopsis and Research], October 5, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - "Alphabet City" by Amos Poe [Inserts and Rewrites], 1983 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - "Alphabet City" by Amos Poe [Revised Script Fragments], c1983 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - "Alphabet City" by Amos Poe [1st Draft Outtakes], June 1983 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - "Alphabet City" An Original Treatment of a Film by Gregory K. Heller, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - "Alphabet City" [Revisions, Etc.], undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - "Alphaville" Treatment, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - "Alphaville," A Treatment by Glenn O'Brien with Amos Poe and Chris Stein, based on a film by Jean Luc Godard, undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - "Artists and Models," Original Treatment by David Salle, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - "Artists and Models," An Original Screen Treatment by David Salle, Amos Poe, and Tony Spiridakis, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - "Artists and Models" [Edits and Notes], c1990 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - "A Sinless Summer" by Damon Galgut [Notes], 1990 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - "The Bad Patch" [Notebook], undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - "The Ballad of Typhoid Mary" by J.F. Federspiel [Notes], undated (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - "Beach House" Treatment by Amos Poe, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - "Beach House" [Script Notes], c1988 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - "The Blank Generation Movie Manifesto" by Amos Poe and Ivan Kral, undated (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - "Bouquet D'Amor" A Proposal by Kim Massee, March 1989 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - "This Bow" by Amos Poe [Partial Script and Notes], March 1990 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - "Bypass" [Scene-by-Scene], August 26, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - "Bypass" [Becker Version], 2000 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - "Bypass" [Developments 2000 - 2004] (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - "Cape Cod Story" [Notes], undated (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - "Chlorine" [Notes], 2001 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - "Cleopatra's Second Husband," Director's Statement by Jon Reiss, c1999 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - "The Correct Sadist," Film Prospectus by Terence Sellers, undated (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Dayrunner Planner [Leather Binder], 1992 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Dayrunner Planner Contents, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - "Dead Weekend" [Notebook], c1995 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - "Diceman Script" [Notes], 1989 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - "Die Tomorrow / Golden Eagle" [Script Notes], 1991 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - "Die Tomorrow / Sunset Eagles" [Notes], 1986 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - "The Domestication of the Vampire," Screen Treatment by Amos Poe, May 1, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - "Enter the Masters (Snake Eyes)" by John Manniel and Amos Poe [Treatment, Outline], undated (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - "The Foreigner" [Notes, Etc.], c1976 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - "The Foreigner" by Amos Poe [Transcript], 1978 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - "Francis Dunn, P.I." by Richard Edson, Amos Poe, and Joel Rose [Treatment, Outline], 1994 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - "Fresh and Firm," A Film Treatment by R. Lester Meyers (Richard Hell), undated (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - "The Golden Eagle" A Proposal for a Work of Non-Fiction by John Manniel and Joel Rose, undated (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - "The Grey Nun" A Treatment for a Thriller by Amos Poe, January 15, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - "The Guitar" [Outline, Notes], January 2002 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - "The Guitar" [Notes], 2003 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - "Hard On Berlin" [Synopsis and Treatment], 1991 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - "The Heart Surgeon" [Notes], c1999 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - "Her Illness" [Notes], undated (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - "Heroes Among Us," A Story Treatment for John Waller by Peter Bakalian, December 1989 (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - "Heroes Among Us" [Notes from John Waller], 1991 (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - "The House With the Gun" by Susan A. Davis, undated (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - "Ice TV" by Mark Levin [Treatment, Notes], June 21, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - "Ice TV / Jihad" [Notebook], 2005 (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - "The Jewess" A Film Treatment by Amos Poe, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - "John the Cop" Interview Tape Transcriptions [Tape 001 - 003], March 18, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - "John the Cop" Interview Tape Transcriptions [Tape 005 - 009], March 18, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - "John the Cop" Transcriptions [Various], undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - "John the Cop" [Notebook], c1996 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - "The Katerpillar" Treatment by Amos Poe, c1998 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - "Kenny Makes A Move" [Notepad], c2001 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - "Kenny Makes A Move" [Fragments, Notes], undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - "Kill the Poor" [Notes], undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - "Land of the Few / Free / Taste of the West" Treatment by Eric Mitchell, undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - "La Pacifica" Reader's Report, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - "La Pacifica" Treatment by Amos Poe, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - "The Last Midnight Show" Synopsis by Amos Poe, undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - "The Late China Max" / "Alison Mac Kinley" A Story by Amos Poe and Nancy Musser, October - November 1984 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - "The Late China Max" Story by Nancy Musser and Amos Poe, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - "The Lodz Seven" / "The Seven" A Screen Treatment by Amos Poe, undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - "The Man From Zimba" [Notes], undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - "Marcello and Teresa" A Screen Treatment by Amos Poe, undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - "Marcello e Teresa" by Amos Poe [Italian], 1982 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - "Marcello and Teresa" [Notes], 1982 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - "The Midnight Show" Synopsis, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - [Misc. Notepad], undated (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - "Mrs. Dogg" [Notes], undated (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - "Mrs. Dogg" [Notepad], undated (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - "Mrs. Dogg" [Notebook], undated (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - "Native Intelligence of the Rebel Breed" Treatment by Amos Poe, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - "Night Witches" [Two Scenes with Annotation], June 6, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - "Night Witches" / "WWII Russian Female Pilots Script" [Britt Harrison to Tony Garnett with Annotation], August 19, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - "Night Witches" [Comments, Notation, Notebook], 2002 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - "One Kiss Too Many" by Amos Poe and Alain Klarer [Various Treatments with Annotation], c1999 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - "The Other Side (of the door)" Treatment by Amos Poe, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - "Paint It Black" [Notes], undated (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - "Paramount Hotel" Treatment by Amos Poe, undated (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - "Port of Call" / "Night Hunt" [Notes], March 1988 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - "The Prince and the Pauper" [Script Meeting Summary and Notes], 1992 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - "The Prince and the Pauper" [Treatments, Etc.], 1992 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - "The Prince and the Pauper" [Notes], undated (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - "The Prince and the Pauper" [Notebook], undated (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - "The Prince and the Pauper" Treatment by Amos Poe, undated (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - "The Queen of Italy" Treatment by Amos Poe, undated (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - "Rebel, Rebel" Treatment, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - "Red Sky" Treatment by Amos Poe and Joel Rose, Story by John Manniel, undated (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - "The Renegade Priest: A Half-Baked Outline" by Ian Kessner [With Annotation], undated (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - "The Renegade Priest" Treatment by Amos Poe and Joel Rose, Based on a Story by John Manniel [With Annotation], undated (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - "Rock 'n Roll Mom" by Marge Suti and Amos Poe, undated (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - "Rocket Gibraltar" [Treatments, Notes], 1985 (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - "Rocket Gibraltar" Treatment by Amos Poe, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - "Rocket Gibraltar" Treatment by Amos Poe [With Annotation], 1985 (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - "Rocket Gibraltar" [Notes], undated (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - "The Roman Ruin" Treatment by Amos Poe, undated (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - "Sacher Torte (Land of My Dreams)" [Treatment and Notes], c1984 (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - "The Savage Garden" by Amos Poe [Introduction with Notes], 1987 (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - "Savage Garden / Scarlet Lips / Port of Call: Notes on Notes", 1987 (Box 13, Folder 53)
    - "The Savage Garden" Treatment by Amos Poe [Revised], December 1987 (Box 13, Folder 54)
    - "Save Our City: An Amos Poe Thang" [Pitch Letters], 1992 (Box 13, Folder 55)
    - "Scarlet Lips" A Preliminary General Scene Breakdown and Story Outline, February 1987 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - "Sealing the Rift / When Broken Clocks Tick / Science Lovers" Treatment by Cookie Mueller, February 22, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - "The Secretary General" [Premise, Notes], March 28, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - "7 x 7: Scott Billingsley, Sara Driver, Bette Gordon, Jim Jarmusch, Eric Mitchell, Amos Poe, Susan Seidelman" Treatment by Amos Poe, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - "The Seville" by Mark Patrick Carducci [Screen Proposal with Annotation], 1984 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - "Showdown At Red Sky" Treatment by Amos Poe and Joel Rose, Story by John Manniel, undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - "Subway Riders" [Transcript Notebook #1], c1979 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - "Subway Riders" [Transcript Notebook #2], c1979 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - "Subway Riders" by Amos Poe [French Translation], 1981 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - "Subway Riders" by Amos Poe [Transcription], 1981 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - "Subway Riders" / "The Rhythm of New York" Treatment by Amos Poe, undated (Box 14, Folder 11)